const setQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `What department handles fake blood?`,
        options: ['SFX', 'Hair', 'Makeup', 'Art'],
        answer: 'Makeup'
    }, {
        id: 2,
        question: `What walkie talkie channel is production usually on?`,
        options: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        answer: '1'
    }, {
        id: 3,
        question: `Which departments work under the lighting director?`,
        options: ['G&E', 'Camera', 'Audio', 'Art'],
        answer: 'G&E'
    }, {
        id: 4,
        question: `What happens when someone not in cast or crew gets on camera?`,
        options: ['An apology', 'An insult', 'Person signs release', 'Production pays them'],
        answer: 'Person signs release'
    }, {
        id: 5,
        question: `What word(s) lets the medic know that they are needed but NOT urgently?`,
        options: ['Bloodless', 'No ambulance', 'Non-emergency', 'No biggie'],
        answer: `Non-emergency`
    }, {
        id: 6,
        question: `What color are crew members asked to wear on set?`,
        options: ['Blue', 'Gray', 'White', 'Black'],
        answer: 'Black'
    }, {
        id: 7,
        question: `What is the name of the Head of the Electric department?`,
        options: ['Best Boy', 'Best Person', 'Gaffer', 'Key Electrcian'],
        answer: `Gaffer`
    }, {
        id: 8,
        question: `What is the name of the Head of the Grip department?`,
        optons: ['Best Boy', 'Gaffer', 'Key Grip', 'Best Boy Grip'],
        answer: 'Key Grip'
    }, {
        id: 9,
        question: `Which crew member writes out camera logs?`,
        options: ['Director of Photography', 'Camera Operator', 'Lighting Director', 'Camera Assistant'],
        answer: 'Camera Assistant'
    }, {
        id: 10,
        question: `Which member of the audio team usually handles mic'ing up cast?`,
        options: ['Audio Supervisor', 'Boom Operator', 'Audio Mixer', 'A2'],
        answer: 'A2'
    }, {
        id: 11,
        question: `Who handles backing up media on set?`,
        options: ['Director of Photography', 'Camera Assistant', 'Audio Mixer', 'Media Manager'],
        answer: 'Media Manager'
    }, {
        id: 12,
        question: `What kind of receipt do PAs need for lunch orders?`,
        options: ['Credit Card', 'Cash', 'Itemized', 'None'],
        answer: 'Itemized'
    }, {
        id: 13,
        question: `What is the itemized list of equipment required when travelling to foreign countries?`,
        options: ['Quote', 'Invoice', 'Carnet', 'Equipment List'],
        answer: 'Carnet'
    }, {
        id: 14,
        question: `What is the term for clearing out equipment and personnel from a location?`,
        options: ['Exit', 'Martini Shot', 'Load Out', 'Load In'],
        answer: 'Load Out'
    }
]